http://www.knittinguniverse.com/privacy

| Search
SEARCH:
GO
Knitting Universe > Privacy Policy
We realize your privacy is very important to you and so it is to us. The following is a summary of what information we collect from you, and how that information is used. What information do we collect?We obtain personal information such as name, e-mail, phone number, address, credit card information, etc. when you place an order through our on-line system. We also track the number of visitors to different pages on our site, but keep no personal information unless an actual order is placed. What are cookies?Cookies are small pieces of information stored on your hard drive that help the website keep track of pages you visited, the fact that you are logged in to your account, which items you have placed in your cart, etc. This information is used to make your shopping experience more enjoyable. We use cookies for other information (including a better user experience for you) as well to gauge the effectiveness of various marketing programs and email campaigns. These cookies are only written if you choose to click on our links and expire after you place an order on knittinguniverse.com. Neither of these forms of cookies retains any personal information whatsoever. They only record which pages you have visited, and provide us information on how well our marketing programs are doing.How is the information we collect used?Internally, we use the information we collect to improve the content of our Web page, and to help us improve the quality of products and services we provide to you. We may also use your e-mail, mailing address or phone number to contact you concerning our services. At no time will we provide any information you provide to sources or companies outside KnittingUniverse.com/XRX, Inc.. We do not sell or trade our customer list. We may also use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, please check back at our website periodically or send us an email. If you do not want us to use your information in one or more of these situations, please email us and let us know in which situation(s) you do not want us to use your information. Please do not forget to include your name and address. Please feel free to contact us with any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy.
KnittingUniverse.com / XRX, Inc. Privacy Policy
The Knitting UniverseKnitter's MagazineXRX BooksSTITCHES EventsCommunity
Create AccountAccount LoginAccount SettingsDownloadsKU StoreContact UsPrivacy PolicyFAQs & Help ArticlesSTITCHESmarket.comStatement of Principles & ConductSubscribeBack IssuesCorrectionsKnitter's Magazine on RavelrystitchipsDigital XRX BooksOrder Books OnlineThe Knitter's HandbookKnit in New DirectionsStitches for Tailored KnitsArtful Color Mindful KnitsBetsy BeadsCustom Knit JacketsEntree to EntrelacGreat American Kids AfghanSwing Swagger DrapeGreat North American AfghanSplendid ApparelKnit My SkirtBest of Weaver's Digital BooksCorrectionsstitchipsXenakis TechniqueHow To RegisterSTITCHES West 2021 CancelledSTITCHES UnitedSTITCHES MidwestSTITCHES SoCalSTITCHES MerchandiseBecome a VendorVendor LoginApply to Teach at STITCHESSacramento, CA AnnouncementSTITCHES 2020 Events - COVID-19 UpdateNew STITCHES Wholesale EventSTITCHES Pro InformationUpdate: STITCHES SoCal 2020 - CancelledXRX Insider NewsletterTwitterRavelry GroupsFacebookInstagramTumblr / BlogGiveawaysBeans for BrainsFiber Hooligan redux
Copyright © 2020 XRX Inc.
